What?
My name is Desmond Miles.
I'm a prisoner of war.
A war I never knew existed.
Waged by two groups I never thought were really Templars.
Animals showed me the truth.
Things I've seen, Things have been 1000 years of history flowing through my veins brought to life by this machine
they're using using me to search for some.
Call it the apple.
It's an artefact.
One of many so called pieces of meat.
Templars collect tell to stay in power.
The Templars get their hands on another one.
Everything will change.
They want to make us all their slaves.
When they first brought me here, I was afraid of what would happen if I tried to fight back.
Now
I'm afraid of what will happen if I don't.
I can't do it alone.
Maybe I don't have to.
I met someone.
Her name is Lucy.
Thinks she's on my side.
She's gone now.
Taken away by the faster Warren.
Vatican is Templar Master's.
I don't know what will happen.
What will happen to me?
All I know is I need to get out of here and I need to do it soon.
My name is Desmond Miles on.
This is my storey
way.
Have to go, Lucy, Where have you been?
Why did they now?
Desmond,
get in.
What's with the blood?
Are you okay?
Look, we have maybe 10 minutes.
Maybe before they figure out what I've done.
If we're not out of here and on the road before, then Wait, We're leaving, Desmond, I promise I'll answer all of your questions later.
But right now, I need you to just shut up and do what I say.
So please, get in the animus.
All right?
Free up.
Yeah.
Come.
Oh,
yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Who?
He's a boy,
my love.
Dispatch.
I was at the bank when they told me.
Did I miss it?
Am I too late?
Give him here.
Jova, my love.
It would be all right
to say an auditory.
So you want combat?
Dainty
metro, Come batty.
Listen to him.
Fine.
Set of lungs on What shall we call him?
My life.
It's you.
It's C o l d told Duffy.
Dancy.
Get up.
Let's go.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna need a second.
There isn't time, Desmond, we have to leave.
Come on, Desmond.
Really getting out of here, huh?
Stay close
That's what I see.
We need to move a common A common.
You're not supposed to be up here.
Open this door or I'm calling it in way.
Have a breach in the research wing.
I replayed up.
There's been a breach in the research over here.
Backup from all available security personnel subjects appear to be armed.
Hurry up.
There they are.
Don't let them get away.
Huh?
Oh,
holy shit.
Come on.
We need to keep moving.
Okay?
Look at this place.
Come on, Desmond.
Let's go.
What about the cameras?
Rigged them toe loop.
Old footage.
How do you think I managed to hide all your nighttime snooping from upstairs?
You're good.
So I've been told.
But they're onto us now.
We need to hurry.
Careful.
We need to get to that elevator on the other side of the room.
Follow my lead, But keep an eye out for security.
I'd rather avoid a fight.
These must be a bitch to clean.
Do you want us to get caught?
Is that an animus?
Stay close,
Apple.
What?
How many of them are there?
Stay close.
He's an animus.
Is stay back.
What do you think, Lucy?
Lucy
No.
What do they need with all of them?
Desmond, shut the fuck up,
please.
Fuck.
I thought this card would work.
It must be on a separate system.
And I don't have the code.
Shit.
Go.
How did you do that?
I don't know.
Let's go.
It's always something.
What was that?
The interest subject.
16.
It's Seo Audi, Audi something.
I think we've been wrong all along.
That's why we need to get out of here.
Vick and the Templars.
There are only part of the problem.
What do you mean?
I'll explain when we get there.
Get where?
No,
no, no,
Well, no.
Move.
No!
Yeah.
No, No,
no,
No.
Well,
Oh, no.
Okay,
get in.
You're joking.
It's for your own protection, and
we're almost there.
Thanks for that was great shoving that.
Trump's bouncing around this way.
So tell me what's going on now?
There was a reason for the escape.
Desmond Figures we need your help.
For what?
Another treasure hunt Through time.
Upstair goes gonna replace their Apple of Eden.
The map your ancestor found guarantees it.
The other assassins.
They'll do what they can where they can.
But what
What is it?
We're losing this war, Desmond.
The Templars are too powerful, and every day more of us die.
I still don't see how I fit into things were going to train you, turn you into one of us.
What?
No, no.
You've seen me in action.
I'm no good at this.
And even if I was, it would take months.
Years even.
No, not with the animus now with the bleeding effect.
But I'm just one guy.
Sometimes that's all you need.
So that's why you found my ancestor.
What was his name?
That seal.
If you can follow in his footsteps, you'll learn everything he did, just like he did.
Years of training absorbed in a matter of days.
You broke me out of hipster go and brought me here just to make me an assassin.
No,
look, there's more to it than that, but it'll have to wait.
Trust me.
Okay.
All right, I'm in.
Tell me what you need.
Really?
You're sure?
I thought you'd be happy about this.
Sorry, I'm just a little surprised.
I spent the whole ride over here figuring out how I was gonna convince you to do this.
Save it.
After what those Templar bastards put me through.
I'm ready, willing and able.
Thank you,
Lucy.
You made it.
God, it's been so long.
Seven years.
Can you believe it?
Indeed.
Welcome back.
S so this must be the infamous subject.
17.
Desmond Miles wasn't.
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
Where are my manners?
I'm Sean Hastings.
This is Rebecca Crane.
Nice to meet you, Desmond.
Right.
Well, it's been lovely chatting, but if you don't mind, Desmond, it's best we get straight toe work.
Time is precious.
Doubly so.
These days we've got everything set up and ready.
Lucy, just say the word.
We'll get going here.
I brought you something.
A parting gift from upstair go.
Whoa.
Memory core.
This is amazing.
With their data things.
They're gonna go a lot faster.
I'll get to work on merging the code.
Hey, listen, I just wanted to say thank you, and I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Yeah.
You know, before everything it up star go.
It was just I wasn't ready.
It's okay.
No going through all that knowing that the Templar still exist.
What they're planning, what's done is done.
Desmond, you're here now.
and that's what matters.
Hey, Desmond, what's up?
Just wondering what your role is in all this I take care of baby.
It's my job to keep her up and running.
Baby, You mean the enemy's?
Actually, I prefer animus.
Two point.
Oh, since babies twice as awesome as anything, you'll find out upstairs.
Go.
The Templars might have deeper pockets than us, but they've got no ambition, no passion, no competitive edge.
That's why even with all their resource is anything they can do, I can do better faster, too.
Anyway, take a seat.
When you're ready and we can get started.
I just need to make a few more adjustments.
What's all this stuff for this stuff?
Desmond, All this stuff is nothing special.
Really.
This stuff is just stuff that keeps our entire operation from falling apart.
Really requires a great deal of concentration to keep it all moving, so you'll forgive me if I don't have time to play, meet and greet Shawn's in charge of maintaining our knowledge archives.
It's like a digital library.
He'll be riding shotgun with me while you're in the animus, so if you come across anything of note people, places events, etcetera.
He'll create database entries.
You can consult for additional information.
Yeah, it's not just databases, though.
I also provide tactical support for the other assassins.
You know, Desmond's the ones who are out there actually doing stuff, risking their lives, little things like that.
You see, I've been seeing things symbols in my bedroom, the code on the keypad, just like l tyre.
It's from the bleeding effect you're taking on more than your ancestors memories.
You're taking on their skills too.
In this case, Eagle vision skills.
You're more receptive now.
So if all goes well, everything at CIA learns in the animus, you'll learn to You really think this will work?
That I'll become an assassin?
You already are an assassin.
You'll just be better at it.
Yeah, every much better at it.
I mean, seriously, I saw the tapes from upstairs.
Go.
You didn't even trying to Skype on a dick.
Sorry, Desmond.
I've got some stuff to take care of.
We can talk more later.
Yeah.
No.
So how does this work?
Of course.
Deep breath.
Oh, where are you?
A tiny child, John.
Well,
here we go.
In.
Selim.
A parallel.
Victoria.
My friends.
That's you.
Do you know what brings us here tonight?
Come on.
The air is imparted Slanders.
My family's name and forces is on miseries are bonus if we enough of your nonsense grew law
the way you were just talking about you.
Surprised to see you here.
I thought the patsy heard others to do their dirty work.
It's your family that cries for guards when there's trouble.
Afraid to handle things yourself.
Your sister seem quite satisfied with handling.
I gave earlier.
You did that alone,
so
yeah.
What?
Okay.
Yeah.
No,
you
Hey, behind you
doing here?
I wanted to see if Baby Brother had finally learned how to fight
there.
And you have style.
But in Jordan's is what counts.
Let's see how many of them you can ruin before they get the best of it.
No.
What?
Let's go.
Oh, you're
No.
Who?
What?
No,
no.
Oh, you're
no
good
clinical.
No.
Yeah!
Oh,
you
back back.
Hold on.
What was one?
These your lips?
That just a scratch that the doctor decided It's not necessary.
Sites have no money for this doctor of yours.
Wasted it on women and wine.
Uh, hardly call it a waste.
Me some flooring is.
Then you've done the same.
Search them.
There's bound to be something in the pockets.
What?
Okay,
what
two?
No.
Yeah.
That should be enough.
Let's get out of here before the guards arrive.
Sorry, it's Seo.
The sooner we're done with the doctor, the sooner we can sleep.
Give it
Frankie here.
Do you require medical assistance?
Ben Trovato, Doctor
for a daily auditory.
Why am I not surprised?
You made quite a mess of yourself, young man.
It's nothing, really.
You must help him.
That pretty face is his only asset.
40.
That's it.
Yeah.
No.
Get out of you
This way.
Fight the night.
Indeed.
I only wish they would always much fun.
Oh, wait.
They are
God.
We should head home at you.
Why?
The show?
To be wondering where we've gone is I'd rather avoid a lecture up for a little race than to wear a roof of the church
on the count of three.
We know.
Do it.
Okay,
baby brother still has much to learn.
Come on out.
Oh, God,
no.
What?
No
baby brother still has much to learn.
Come on.
Haruka.
Yeah.
Come on.
This way.
Way I'm going.
You'll see
it is a good life.
We leave, brother.
Yeah
based.
Never change on May never change us.
No.
All right, enough way really should head.
Let's go.
Wait.
But
at CEO, that Christine asleep There will be time enough for that later.
Uh,
yeah.
So it's Vietti.
Better hide.
Keep looking.
He couldn't have gotten far.
You?
No.
Yes.
What?
Okay.
Yeah,
fine.
Dina?
Dina!
Who's that?
Me.
Oh, it's you.
I should have known.
May I go mean Fine, But only for a minute.
A minute to sell?
I need indeed were way Teo came out wrong.
Come here.
No!
Oh!
Oh, it's you,
Christina.
Christina
will be here soon.
Come, my daughter.
Is it really so terrible that?
What is this?
If
you don't, I'll kill you.
Now That's not necessary.
Gods!
Gods, What are you doing?
That's what past stuff.
Now there's really no need for violence.
We could try.
You have me confused with someone else my way.
She needed some help with some things.
I'm mostly innocent.
What?
Okay, wait.
Oh,
morning!
And
members have hashed browns from me suspecting a beautician in the copper delivered.
Thank you.
No way.
Okay.
Yeah.
Another smooth on him.
See?
Yeah.
Just
so Billy to the game,
right?
Yeah.
No.
What?
You know where you are?
It's raining on the wisdom of the Arab way.
No,
no.
You from the dead?
I don't see
only a truly depraved So, Bill, today I rest leashes.
Today
I am making Gore does for the next I
Yeah,
farewell and swift recovery of me aboutthe rotation of
ready
John.
Good morning, Father.
Come with me.
Something wrong?
Do you think me blind and death, son,
I know all about your fight with the patsy last night and then this little visit.
Christina,
your behaviour is unacceptable.
It
it's
It reminds me of myself when I was your age.
I assume these misadventures wanted to fear What?
Your work today?
No, Padre Della Mia Parola.
I've prepared some documents here for Lorenzo de Medici to review.
I need them delivered to him.
We faced Father.
They tend to me when it's done.
Magnificat Lorenzo de Medici Mu predatory amigo, I have done as requested and completed my investigation into the Milano incident.
I can confirm for you that it extends far beyond the satisfaction with took a guard.
Liatsos forces the rule.
It is my belief that other parties desires a far greater gains, manipulated events in such a way as to achieve their goals without being revealed themselves.
Lampoon Yanni or John Gotti and Visconti are guilty of the crime, to be sure,
and they have met fitting ends for their betrayal.
But several other noble families are implicated as well.
Our own Francesco Di Patsy among them.
Their cause and motive is not yet clear to me.
But initial findings indicated plan scope of which is sure to disturb you best.
We continue this conversation in person as I am hesitant to put my suspicion to paper
reply with a place in time and I wouldn't meet you there.
I have also ordered Francesco be held by the Confalonieri until we can clear up this matter.
Yours in confidence.
Giovanni?
Yeah,
honey.
Chief,
it's going
not exactly broke that out of a ring of impertinence
has nothing on me.
I have this shot close of all.
No
this way.
I also have
every Renaissance community needed.
A blacksmith.
Swords, locks, pans, knives, nails and armour were all made from metal in all needed to be shaped.
In addition, architectural ironwork flourished during the Renaissance as blacksmiths began to apply their practical craft towards making art.
Look for my brother sports very attractive, right?
Miss?
What?
Yeah,
I may be expensive, but my goods are worth the extra.
I've never smoked.
Shoddy.
Mmm.
Oh,
what?
What?
You know your stuff?
No.
Shall we have some time after the execution?
Ah, it's Ben.
Tre.
How are you?
Miss Embry?
I have a letter for him.
Several Lorenzo.
I'll see that he receives it when he returns.
Returns.
They've gone to Villa Correggio, I'm afraid.
And not expected Back for at least another day.
I let my father know.
Oh, no,
He's okay.
Bye.
Yeah.
No, no.
Here, Max.
No.
That What?
Up yours
A lot.
Hello?
Hi, Max.
What?
Yeah,
Better not be looking for trouble.
Where?
Yeah.
No.
What?
Healing services for all of God's flock.
Oh, my.
Yeah.
Yes,
I am.
Among Renaissance merchants.
Taylor's belonged to the new middle class and were paid well for clothing.
The rich in the latest fashions, many were able to get close to their wealthy clients due to the intimacy of their job and create lasting ties.
Wait,
Promises.
Like
careful with that.
I should make you pay for that.
Not what
you're Yeah,
No way.
So,
yeah.
Keep up the good work.
Be skittle.
You worry too much,
Francesco de parties in prison.
The threat is ended.
Hello, son.
You remember my friend Morning, Confalonieri.
Alberti to you as well, Young man, I trust you delivered the message.
See, Padre?
But it seems Lorenzo is out of town.
I did not anticipate this.
What does it matter?
So you wait another day or two.
Listen, your mother and sister have been looking for you.
I'll need you again in a little while.
But for now, see if you can't help him.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
Good to see you at you.
No
date of birth.
14.
61 Profession.
Student Noble The third child of Giovanni and Maria Auditory and the first girl in the family.
Claudia seems to have been a bit of a spoiled brat.
It looks like her parents had to raise her dowry by 1000 florins after she's scared away all her potential suitors.
A report from her school indicates she once attacked another girl for looking at her boyfriend and knocked her out cold.
On the plus side, she's at Seo's sister.
So you should be safe,
huh?
No.
Claudia, How are you?
Danny?
You shouldn't keep things from me.
It's a lucha.
What of him?
I think he's been unfaithful.
Who told you this?
The other girls
I thought they were.
My friends are apiece.
You're better off without them.
I loved.
You know, Claudia, you only thought you did.
He should suffer for what he's done.
Wait here.
I'll go have a word with him.
No.
No,
Scott.
What?
Do what?
You It's a beautiful nothing but the best for you.
More than you.
But what of Claudia?
I thought you'd been promised.
Her father said they could do much better than an Audi toad.
Oh, bunting.
Come let us walk a big What?
I had something else.
Oh, do you?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, Louie, The portico.
It's Theo, my friend.
Get the media.
You insult my sister parading around with his katana.
What are you talking about?
I saw the gift you gave her.
But the things you said maybe your sister shouldn't be so stingy with her too.
You broke her heart
and now I'm going to break your face.
You wanted to talk, but when it comes time for action,
you'll regret ever opening your mouth.
I could have bought your sister A great many things started off
stock.
Bye bye.
Busted.
Why my stay away from my sister.
Oh,
always
on your faces.
Not for you.
No.
What?
Run!
Oh, plus
Hey, you!
Are you doing out here through Chou?
You should be in bed.
I want those feathers.
What for?
It's a secret if I get them for you when you go back inside.
Yes, I promise.
Where?
But
no.
Okay.
No.
Oh
one
don't.
You're ready.
That should he?
I'm living off nothing.
Bye.
Yeah,
here.
As promised.
Your brother.
You still haven't told me why you want these.
I will in time.
Okay.
Way from
me.
When Jordan Lloyd's hell one Giordano avoid Marjorie may start still banning.
And you
still recovering from last night?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Of course.
Know Anyway, I have an errand to run.
I'd like you to join Compete Cherry.
Come on.
It's not far from here.
I know about your fight With
what fight?
Let's not play this game.
You spoke ill of us.
I could not allow him to continue.
I'm sure he's having a hard time dealing with the accusations against his father.
Francesco de Part sees many things, none of them good.
But even I never suspected he'd be capable of murder.
What happened to him?
I imagine that would be a triumph.
Your father speak at the he'll have to.
He's the one with the evidence.
It's a deal.
I wish there was another way.
You have nothing to fear.
Everyone wants justice done.
It is an unfortunate state of affairs, but it will pass.
With the advent of double entry bookkeeping, which allowed bankers to keep track of their clients deposits and withdrawals, and the proliferation of many different types of Italian currency into the pool of circulation banks became an essential part of every day.
Renaissance life banks technically couldn't make money on their money because the Catholic Church forbade the charging of interest.
But in practise, this restriction wasn't followed by bankers or even by the Vatican, which participated in the banking system and required banks to pay the pope gifts in proportion to the amount of money he had deposited with them.
As long as it isn't called interest.
God won't notice.
Right?
No.
All right.
Here we are.
Okay.
No.
Hello, Leonardo.
Madonna.
Maria,
this is my son
Nora and me.
Let me go and fetch the paintings.
I'll be right back.
It's a very talented, A marginal self.
Expression is vital to understanding and enjoying life.
You should find an outlet.
I have plenty of outlets.
I meant besides vaginas.
Mother.
Back to your house, then.
Si, si.
It's you help lay on our though, will you?
So it's you.
What do you do?
He's been working for his father.
Um, you're to be a banker for now.
On you art, was it?
No.
Truth be told, it's been difficult for me to set.
Painting is nice, but I often feel like my work legs.
I don't know what purpose does that make sense?
I'd rather contribute more practically more directly.
Architecture.
Perhaps it or anatomy and not content merely to capture the world.
I want to change it.
So now I have no doubt you'll go on to do great things.
He didn't get you.
That's kind of you.
Thank you for your help, son.
Don't let me keep you from your other duties.
It was nice to meet you at you.
I hope our paths cross again.
Ankiel.
He's on leave.
Thank you.
Got to go.
Date of birth.
14 52.
Profession painter, inventor, designer, architect, scientist, engineer.
The illegitimate son of a notary and a peasant woman, Leonardo da Vinci was raised in Tuscany.
Like many destined to be superstars, he had no surname.
Vinci being the town in which he was born at age 14, he was apprenticed to a floor Indian painter Varro Keogh, who taught him chemistry, drafting, painting, sculpting and modelling.
When he was 20 Leonardo established his own workshop and then travelled across Italy, eventually painting his great masterpieces The Last Supper in 14 98 and the Mona Lisa in 15 Oh 3 to 7.
During his travels, Leonardo studied the world with unquenchable curiosity, recording his observations in mirror writing.
Within his notebooks, he created designs for a helicopter, tanks, solar power and a calculator, among others.
He was also an engineer, designing garrisons, cannons and moveable barricades.
Despite this epic list of accomplishments, Leonardo was hounded by his patrons for his chronic procrastination.
Pieces frequently took years longer than he anticipated, and many were never finished at all.
Leonardo also had a tumultuous love life, accused of sodomy and 14 76 he was most likely homosexual.
Sly, his assistant, was accused of stealing and spending too much money on clothes, but was also probably Leonardo's lover.
Leonardo painted several pictures of Sly, including his famous ST John the Baptist, and left the Mona Lisa to him when he died in 15 19
date of birth.
14 36.
Profession.
Banker advisor Noble Giovanni Auditory was one of the pivotal figures in 15th century Florentine banking in charge of overseeing the Medici bank branches across Italy.
He kept the Medici machine running while Lorenzo was busy with the government, extending his reach out into the international operation.
It was Giovanni who first noticed the problems with a land bank, causing him to alert Francesco Society, which saved the branch.
Such great talent was well rewarded by Il Magnifico.
Giovanni developed a close friendship with Lorenzo de Medici, becoming one of his closest advisers.
Successful negotiations to secure the pope's support of the Medici Bank in 14 71 were carried out by Giovanni.
Relieved and grateful, Lorenzo paid for Giovanni's palazzo as a gift.
One of Italy's largest churches in the largest landmark in Florence, Santa Maria del Fiore, is considered by many to be the first masterpiece of Renaissance architecture.
Although the church was designed by Arnulfo de Cambio in 12 96 the dome was not started until the beginning of the 15th century, with Camby a long dead.
None of the architects at that time had any idea how to construct such an enormous structure, since the use of buttresses was forbidden in Florence and mortar took several days to send.
But all was not lost.
In an amazing comeback Storey Filippo Brunelleschi, an architect who had been defeated in an earlier bid to design the Baptist re doors, won the competition to build the dome.
He beat out Lorenzo Gah Bertie, the same artist.
He had lost it before.
Brunelleschi's invented machines to hoist the bricks needed for the dome up to the workers and was able to construct the entire dome without using centering a support structure to hold the dome in place.
While bricks were laid containing over four million bricks.
The dome was completed in 14 36.
The lantern was added after Brunelleschi's death in 14 46 and supposedly contains holy relics.
However, there were several rumours that in fact an entire tomb of unknown origin is located inside
date of birth.
14 63 Profession.
Student Noble The youngest of the auditory Children, Petruchio was described as having a weak constitution by Giovanni Auditory in a letter to Lorenzo de Medici soon after the boy's birth.
Apparently he didn't improve with time.
Petruchio was pulled from school due to illness when he was 12 and, according to records from the family doctor, was confined to bed.
No other data exists after that, so it is probable that he eventually succumbed to his illness.
Date of Birth.
14 32 Profession.
Writer Noble I grow tired of these walls that surround me, and I'm bored with safety.
Now is the time to make a decision.
I will go out there and see what my life may truly be.
Maria wrote those words when she was 16, a week before she met Giovanni Auditory, born into a powerful banking family, the moat see Maria is one of the most famous historical sources of the time period due to her multi volume diary, which has been translated by several notable scholars and is on display in the Youth Fitzy Gallery in Florence.
With funding from her parents, Maria opened up a bakery in the courtyard of her family palazzo, which she transformed into an artistic gathering place.
It was there that she met a man with such conviction.
I found myself rooted to the spot, unable to look anywhere else.
That man was Giovanni, Auditory.
Maria and Giovanni were married in 14 50.
Maria's Diary entries continue for the next few decades, describing her patronage of several up and coming artists and her trials as a mother, at which point she abruptly abandons her writing to the disappointment of historians everywhere.
Shops of Renaissance artists were usually small and dealt mainly, and religious decorations for churches or homes.
Artists were not considered visionaries as there today, but we're treated merely is craftsman, just like carpenters and blacksmiths.
The production of art was usually cooperative.
The head of the shop was the master who received commissions and oversaw the assembly of the painting.
He was expected to be a businessman and turn a profit, usually creating copies of whatever religious paintings were in vogue at the time.
Diagrams of the human body and the printing press influenced Renaissance Medicine greatly, which had in turn been influenced by Arabic medicine during the Middle Ages.
By the 15th century, science had already begun its slow climb toward becoming more relevant than spirituality.
In the field of health care, however, many people stubbornly cling to old ways, visiting local mystics instead of doctors.
After the plague ravaged Europe in 13 50 many doctors dressed in special plague gear to treat patients to prevent contamination.
They wore a cape coated in wax and a primitive gas mask in the shape of a big
date of birth.
14 59.
Profession student noble Christina Vespucci was a well known Florentine beauty and a favourite of painters, most notably BOTTICELLI, who used her as a model for several of his paintings.
Records kept by her father's guards indicated CEO visited her frequently and that he was unbelievably dextrous as the guards were never able to catch him trespassing.
In addition to her looks, Christina also seems to have been somewhat responsible for jump starting the career of her cousin, the namesake of a rather famous land Mass.
At a dinner party attended by Christina and, among other illustrious guests, Lorenzo de Medici.
She was reputed to have been in conversation with Lorenzo and Mon Fredo Santorini, about her cousin's brilliance as a sailor.
Well, apparently she exaggerated his important slightly to impress.
Lorenzo and Lorenzo, charmed by her beauty, agreed to hire him.
Try Amerigo out, I bet after several years you'll name your shipping company after him, she is reported to have joked.
Biggest understatement of the century.
Date of birth.
14 56 profession.
Student Noble Seo's older brother and the eldest Audi Torrey Federico entered the Medici bank is a clerk when he was 19.
However, the bank logs indicate he mostly dicked around rather than actually working.
One entry goes into detail.
On September 17th, 14 75 a bag of gold Florence went missing after panic struck the bank.
The elder auditory approached Francesco Society and with a smile, revealed the location of the back, which had been hidden on the rooftop.
If he weren't the son of Giovanni Auditory, I'd speak to Lorenzo de Medici and have him put in the stocks.
Unsurprisingly, Federico was removed from the bank's payroll shortly after his 20th birthday.
Date of birth.
14 59.
Profession.
Student Noble in a diary entry from 14 70 for Maria Auditory, one of the great Florentine chroniclers and that CEO's mother describes her son, is competitive, stubborn and loud mouthed, but so passionate that it is impossible to fault him for anything.
Complaints to the city Guard by several noble patricians seemed to suggest he was also something of a womaniser tutored by the great banker Giovanni.
TOURNEY BOLOGNA Lazio school records cease around age 17, at which point his name is connected with some terrible crime.
It is impossible to discern what it could be from the records.
There's very little here, but afterward that Seo drops out of history entirely as if he never existed.
Completed in 14 73 the Palazzo auditory is notable for its rusticated stonework in Roman pilasters.
Giovanni Auditory designed the Palazzo himself, based on initial sketches by Leon Battista Alberti.
Once built, the Palazzo became a fixture of the Santa Maria novella district.
Lorenzo de Medici, mentioned in a letter addressed to Giovanni, dated 14 74 that he admired the facades lack of ostentation
built by a distant great great uncle of the famous Americo Vespucci.
And 13 50 the relatively un presumptuous Vespucci residents is notable for displaying the first painted facade in Florence, a style that was later done to death in the car No district,
constructed over an existing church in 12 58 Santa Trinita.
Holy Trinity is known for its society chapel, which is decorated with frescoes of the Life of ST Francis by Domenico Garland.
I owe a painter.
Most famous for his brief role is one of Michelangelo's teachers.
Santa Trinita was the mother.
Church of the Valen grows in order of monks, a very serious route that strictly enforced both poverty and silence for life.
Despite the beauty of the Santa Trinita frescoes, very few vellum rose and monks are likely to have seen that on account of the fact that the monks received beatings for going outside their monasteries.
Founded by Julius Caesar in 59 BC, Floren chalet, as it was called by the Romans, quickly became a centre of commerce.
After the sacking of Rome in the fifth century, the Ostro Goths took over under their rule the city was constantly under attack from the Byzantines, who sent the population level below 1000.
The Lombard came to power in the sixth century, ending the Byzantine assaults.
Florence grew to a population of 80,000 in the 14th century, of which 25,000 were working in the wool industry.
In 13 78 a major revolt of the lower class led to the wolf Homer's rising up and seizing the government of the city.
They're progressive.
Radical Democracy lasted for less than two months before the upper classes seized control once more.
But the revolt so terrified the rich that a century later it was still discussed in hushed tones.
Much of the 19 sixties hippy movement is today.
The L busy family became the de facto rulers after the revolt, worried about the rise of the Medici family, who were newly rich bankers rapidly gaining influence in Florence.
Maso and Ronaldo al busy imprison Cosimo de Medici and exiled him in 14 33.
But Cosimo gained influence behind the scenes and rose to power in 14 30 for exiling the entire al busy family.
Except for Luca, who had been loyal to Cosimo Luca Al busy joined the scenario.
The ruling body of Florence asking Fallon near succeeding.
Cosimo is old friend Ilario Auditory and 14 42 under the Medici family, which built impressive public buildings and supported such luminaries as Michelangelo, Leonardo and BOTTICELLI.
The Renaissance began with Florence securely at its centre
happened here.
Oh, God,
no!
Well,
well.